A hometown kid on his BMX against the best in the
world. At Helltrack... the heat is on.
Rad is a drama, family film directed by Hal Needham.
A BMX racer, who lives in a small town with his mother and sister, is faced with a tough
decision, qualify for Helltrack or take his SATs in order to attend college.
Cru, played by Bill Allen.
Christian, played by Lori Loughlin.
Mrs. Jones, played by Talia Shire.
Burton Timmer, played by Ray Walston.
Eliott Dole, played by Alfie Wise.
Duke Best, played by Jack Weston.
Rad (international title: Hell Track) is a 1986 American sports film directed by Hal Needham from a
screenplay by Sam Bernard and Geoffrey Edwards (son of Pink Panther creator Blake Edwards).
The film stars Bill Allen, Lori Loughlin, Talia Shire, Jack Weston and Ray
Walston, along with 1984 Olympic gymnastics champion Bart Conner.
The film under-performed at the box office, grossing $2 million against a
budget of $3 million, and received mixed reviews from critics.
The tone is emotional.